At the beginning of every term we invite new students and their parents
보드웰에서는 매 학기 시작마다 신입생과 부모님을 초대해서
for a comprehensive new student orientation where they can tour the facilities
학생과 부모님이 학교를 투어하고 다양한 프레젠테이션에 참여할 수 있는
and attend various presentations to help prepare them for the year
오리엔테이션이 준비되어 있습니다
New students and parents begin by checking in couple of days before the orientation starts.
신입생과 부모님은 오리엔테이션 시작 며칠전에 기숙사에 체크인합니다
It's a busy time of the year. It's time to mingle meet other - especially the volunteers
오리엔테이션 주간은 일년중 바쁜 때로 학생 자원봉사자,
and to also meet the boarding staff will help direct you over the next couple of days
기숙사 스텝이 다음 며칠간의 일정을 안내해줍니다
Depending on when you arrive you will have a couple of days to relax and unpack
학생은 체크인 하는 날로부터 며칠 동안 짐을 정리하며 쉴 수 있고
Take a tour of the facility
스텝과 학생 자원봉사자로부터 안내받아서
Meet staff and student volunteers that will guide you on a tour of Bodwell or help direct you where to go
학교를 둘러볼 수 있습니다
There are lots of signs around the school to help you as well we have coffee we have snacks available
학교에는 여러가지 안내가 잘 표시되어 있고 커피와 간식거리가 준비되어 있습니다
As orientation begins it's an extremely busy time for new students and their parents
오리엔테이션이 시작되면 신입생과 부모님은 상당히 바쁜 일정을 보내게 되지만
However, it is all done in a relaxed atmosphere and we accommodate and appreciate that everybody is new.
모두가 신입생을 반기는 분위기 속에서 편안하게 일정을 소화해가며
So we're here to offer help the students to adjust
학생이 부담없이 도움받아서 잘 적응할 수 있도록 합니다
When orientation begins students and parents will have to follow different schedules during this time, it's a very busy schedule for students
오리엔테이션이 시작되면 학생과 부모님은 각각 다른 일정을 따릅니다
They have to meet the principals and admin
학생은 교장선생님과 교무팀을 만나고
they have to do a placement test
반편성 시험을 치루며
They will attend the citizenship presentation where they'll be exposed to various leadership activities around school
시민사회 프레젠테이션에 참가해서 다양한 리더십 활동에 대해 듣습니다
They'll be fitted for their uniform
교복을 맞추고
They will attend a laptop distribution session and you'll be briefed about how to use their new laptops.
노트북 분배 세션 동안 어떻게 노트북을 사용해야 하는지 배우며
They'll attend presentation on safety
안전에 관한 프레젠테이션을 듣고
They will also attend a presentation about Block E
토요 심화 학습, 방과후 활동 프레젠테이션에 참여합니다
and extracurricular activities and various athletic teams around school. They will do a neighborhood walk
학생들은 학교 주변을 걸으면서
So they're familiar with the school and its surroundings
학교와 학교 주변에 익숙해지게 됩니다
They will attend a group orientation with their counselors followed by one-on-one for their course selection
또한 카운셀러와의 단체 오리엔테이션에 참가한 뒤 일대일로 과목 선정을 합니다
They will also attend boarding life and house orientations
기숙사 생활과 하우스에 관한 오리엔테이션도 준비되어 있습니다
We also help our students with opening a bank account by inviting one of the local banks to come to Bodwell
학교는 지역 은행원을 보드웰로 초청해서 학생이 은행 계좌를 만들 수 있도록 도와줍니다
Parents will have their own separate schedule. They to get to meet the principals and the admin team
부모님은 학생과는 다른 일정을 갖습니다. 부모님들도 교장선생님과 교무팀을 만나고
They attend a presentation about boarding and homestay programs
기숙사 및 홈스테이 프로그램 프레젠테이션을 들으며
They tour the City of North Vancouver Vancouver and West Vancouver
노스밴쿠버, 밴쿠버, 웨스트밴쿠버 투어를 합니다
They attend orientation with counselors and they can request one-on-one meeting with their counselors
또한 카운셀러와의 오리엔테이션에 참관하면서 카운셀러와 일대일 미팅을 요청할 수도 있습니다
they get a chance to network with other parents and with school administrators and
다른 부모님들 및 교무팀 직원을 만날 수 있고
They also attend a presentation about graduation requirements and post-secondary discussion
졸업 요건 및 대학에 관한 프레젠테이션을 듣습니다
There are many activities parents and students do together - a briefing by the police department
경찰서의 브리핑 같은 경우 부모님과 학생이 같이 참여하게 됩니다
Start of the term assembly and most mealtimes are spent together
조례가 시작되고 대부분의 식사는 같이 할 수 있습니다
During orientation is a lot to take in but be assured
오리엔테이션은 많은 일을 치루게 되지만
there is lots of time to say goodbye to your child meet the staff who will take care of your child and
부모님이 학생과 작별할 수 있는 충분한 시간을 갖고
Meet other parents and families who are also new to the Bodwell community
학생을 돌봐줄 스텝들과 인사하며 다른 학부모님과 가족들을 만날 수 있습니다